("Party Up" by DMX)
♪ Woo! ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me lose my mind ♪
♪ Up in here, up in here ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me go all out ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me act a fool ♪
♪ Up in here, up in here ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me lose my cool ♪
♪ If I gotsta bring it to you cowards ♪
♪ Then it's gonna be quick, aight ♪
♪ All your mens up in the jail before ♪
♪ Suck my, woo ♪
♪ And all them other cats you run with ♪
♪ Get done with, dumb quick. ♪
♪ How the F you you gonna cross ♪
♪ The dog with some bum ♪
♪ Aight, There go the ♪
♪ One one ♪
♪ All over some dumb ♪
♪ Ain't that some ♪
♪ Remind me of a strip club ♪
♪ Cause every time you come around ♪
♪ It's like I just gotta get my sucked. ♪
♪ And I don't know who the ♪
♪ You think you talking to ♪
♪ But I'm not him, aight slim ♪
♪ So watch what you do ♪
♪ Or you gon' find yourself,
next to someone else ♪
♪ And we all thought you loved yourself ♪
♪ But that couldn't a been the issue ♪
♪ Or maybe they just sayin' that ♪
♪ Now cause they miss you ♪
♪ Maybe they tried to diss you ♪
♪ That's why you're laying on your back ♪
♪ Looking at the roof of the church ♪
♪ Preacher telling the
truth and it hurts ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me lose my mind ♪
♪ Up in here, up in here ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me go all out ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me act a fool ♪
♪ Up in here, up in here ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me lose my cool ♪
♪ Off the chain I leave ♪
♪ Soft in the brain, ♪
♪ Still want the fame ♪
♪ Off the name ♪
♪ First of all, you ain't
rapped long enough ♪
♪ To be (crashing) with me ♪
♪ You ain't strong enough ♪
♪ So whatever it is you puffin on ♪
♪ That got you thinking
that you Superman ♪
♪ I got the Kryptonite and I
smack you with my (slapping) ♪
♪ And the mic (glass shatters) ♪
♪ Y'all is characters,
not even good actors ♪
♪ What's gon' be the outcome, hmm, ♪
♪ Let's add up all the factors. ♪
♪ You wack, you're twisted,
your girl's a whoo ♪
♪ You broke, the kid ain't
yours, and everybody knows ♪
♪ Your old man say you
stupid, you be like ♪
♪ "So, I love my baby
mother, I never let her go" ♪
♪ I'm tired of weak (baby
crying) whining over ♪
♪ That don't belong to them,
what's wrong with them ♪
♪ (Punching) for real
like my mans and them ♪
♪ Who get it on on the strength
of the hands with them, man ♪
♪ Y'all gon make me lose my mind ♪
♪ Up in here, up in here ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me go all out ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me act a fool ♪
♪ Up in here, up in here ♪
♪ Y'all gon make me lose my cool ♪
- Yeah
- Big Gap whaddup, I'm in trouble, yo,
you know I only call you when I need you.
- You know I'm at your dispense, baby.
- I knew I could count on you dog.
- Be right on my way
over in 15 minutes, man.
- Word.
♪ I bring down rains so
heavy it curse the head ♪
♪ No more talking, put
him in the dirt instead ♪
♪ You keep walking, unless
you're trying to end up red ♪
♪ Cause if I end up fed, y'all end up ♪
♪ Cause youse the soft type ♪
♪ What ♪
♪ Fake up North type ♪
♪ Like a soft white (trilling) ♪
♪ Dog is a dog, blood's
thicker than water ♪
♪ We done been through
the mud and (whistles) ♪
♪ We run up in there, e'rybody come out ♪
♪ Don't nobody run out ♪
♪ Sun in, sun out, I'mma keep the out ♪
♪ Running his mouth, I'mma a out ♪
♪ Listen, is about to be missing ♪
♪ You know who gon find you ♪
♪ Who ♪
♪ Some old man fishing ♪
♪ Grandma wishing your (whistles) ♪
♪ But it's hard to digest with
the size of the (whistles) ♪
♪ Y'all gon' make me lose my mind ♪
♪ Up in here, up in here ♪
♪ Y'all gon make me go all out ♪
- Seems as though there are
a couple of suburbans pulling up
and female's are running everywhere.
♪ Y'all gon' make me act a fool ♪
♪ Up in here, up in here ♪
- Just say the word.
- Take the shot, take the shot.
- Don't shoot, that's not the right man!
♪ One, Two, meet me outside ♪
♪ Meet me outside, meet me outside ♪
♪ All my, Ruff Ryders,
gon' meet me outside ♪
♪ Meet me outside, meet me outside ♪
♪ All my, big ballers,
gon' meet me outside ♪
♪ Meet me outside, meet me outside ♪
♪ All my, fly ladies,
gon' meet me outside ♪
♪ Meet me outside, meet me outside ♪
♪ All my street, street, people ♪
♪ Meet me outside, meet me outside. ♪